stalkerville.net 2014-12-02

# Privacy and Disclosure Statement - Stalkerville

We collect information you give us when you use our site in various ways including when you register on our site, make submissions, subscribe to our newsletter, fill out a form or leave a comment.

Like most other sites, we collect the type of computer, browser, and web service you are using. We also collect the date, time, pages you visit, and if you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. The information we collect from you may be used to personalize your experience, improve our website, administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature or send periodic emails.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction.  If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

We also participate in various affiliate programs such as Amazon which generates a small commission when you make a purchase via a link from our site. We are not provided any details about who makes purchases from any of these affiliates.

This policy was last modified on September 14, 2013

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us through our [contact form](http://stalkerville.net/contact-us/).
